<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>salemwala.best</title>
    <link>https://alisalemwala.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on salemwala.best</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 19:04:44 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alisalemwala.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Recruited</title>
      <link>https://alisalemwala.github.io/posts/getting-recruited/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 19:04:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alisalemwala.github.io/posts/getting-recruited/</guid>
      <description>##Getting Recruited
The money is in tech, and so is the freedom. I have friends working in other fields, being pushed around by power-tripping assholes for a pittance of wages. In tech, the power-tripping assholes have to pay you a lot of money, and you only get pushed around in Zoom calls you take from sunny beaches while you work remotely. This spoils you, and I want all my friends to be as spoilt as I&amp;rsquo;ve become, so I&amp;rsquo;ve taken to telling everybody I meet to join the tech industry, agriculture and the arts be damned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relationships and Memories: 3 Movie Sunday</title>
      <link>https://alisalemwala.github.io/posts/relationships-and-memories-3-movie-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 22:02:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alisalemwala.github.io/posts/relationships-and-memories-3-movie-sunday/</guid>
      <description>I finally did it. I genuinely spent a whole Sunday doing nothing, and feeling no guilt over it. Not an easy feat.
Friday was nice. A bar, a cute girl with a boyfriend, getting lost in a farm.
Saturday was fun. Waking up to a phone call at noon, my guy asking for his jacket back from the night before. Regret and confusion for everything that happened. An introduction to a ski course at some crazy guy&amp;rsquo;s home, out in the boondocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gym Routines</title>
      <link>https://alisalemwala.github.io/posts/gym-routines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 19:18:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alisalemwala.github.io/posts/gym-routines/</guid>
      <description>This should be one long saga.
My body has embarrassed me all my life. I&amp;rsquo;ve fantasized about being Jacked &amp;amp; Tan™ since my prepubescent days. I gathered the courage to accompany a couple of my other chump friends when I was around 14, I&amp;rsquo;d say. It was pathetic. I then fantasized for a couple more years, until I was 16 or 17. After that, I went pretty regularly (all in secret, of course), and plodded along following whatever nonsense the trainer there told me to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading</title>
      <link>https://alisalemwala.github.io/posts/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 18:26:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alisalemwala.github.io/posts/reading/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t ask me what reading is because I don&amp;rsquo;t know. Over the past two and almost-a-half decades of my life, it was a lot of different things to me.
Reading is a gleaming bubble of soap you can sink into, when the world around you is a heap of stinking sewage. The smell doesn&amp;rsquo;t hit you, the filth doesn&amp;rsquo;t reach you, and the flies buzzing around melt into the sound of the blood pounding in your ears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diet</title>
      <link>https://alisalemwala.github.io/posts/diet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 15:06:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alisalemwala.github.io/posts/diet/</guid>
      <description>Turkey: I lived here from August 2015 to May 2021. I started out as a university student on a strict self-appointed budget, and transitioned into an extremely highly paid professional without any budget really, but with a focus on remaining economical wherever possible. What this means is, I started to enjoy myself and indulge in little (and sometimes not so little) pleasures. On the whole, however, I did not move onto luxury.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making This</title>
      <link>https://alisalemwala.github.io/posts/making-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 20:47:59 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alisalemwala.github.io/posts/making-this/</guid>
      <description>Making something like this is as simple as it looks. There were a few things I wrestled with, mainly GitHub submodules, but I ended up getting through. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain them further down, both for your sake and my own. I know I&amp;rsquo;ll forget it all in a week.
Note: It has been exactly 8 weeks since I wrote that note above. I still have not completed this post. I remember absolutely nothing from when I first made it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://alisalemwala.github.io/about-salemwala/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alisalemwala.github.io/about-salemwala/</guid>
      <description>This drab, gray website is an acccurate expression of my soul. The best About Me section would be blank page, with two Spider-Men pointing at each other, but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how many of your working hours you can waste staring at that. Thus, these words. Hopefully, your working hours are for the HR or recruiting department for a next-gen, cutting-edge, all-the-bells-and-whistles startup, and these billed and wasted hours can be shared with me, in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Bullshit</title>
      <link>https://alisalemwala.github.io/posts/hugo-bullshit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alisalemwala.github.io/posts/hugo-bullshit/</guid>
      <description>Migrate Hugo to Jekyll Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
